hollisterco.jp 2018-05-04

# privacy-and-terms

Updated: January 2018

In order to make your visits to the various online channels of Hollister Co. as responsive as possible, we provide this summary of what information we collect online, and how that information is used.

This privacy policy statement applies only to the information collected online through HollisterCo.jp, Hollister Co. microsites or mobile sites (collectively our “Websites”), our communications, social media sites and accounts, or mobile applications that Hollister Co. provides for download to your mobile device ("Apps") that expressly adopt, and display or link to, this policy.

The information you provide through our Websites, Apps, communications and through social media sites and accounts is collected by Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc. and processed by Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc., Abercrombie & Fitch Management Co., AFH Japan GK, and AFH HK DTC Limited.

### Contents

  * What is Personal Data
  * Information We Collect Online
  * Mobile Application
  * Information Collected on Pages Hollister Co. has on Social Media Sites
  * Using Information We Collect
  * Information We Share With Third Parties
  * Storage of Information
  * Cookies and Advertising
  * Consent
  * Opt-Out
  * Accessing and Updating Your Personal Data
  * Privacy of Children
  * Links
  * Updates to Privacy Policy 
  * Security Statement
  * Questions About Privacy

### What is Personal Data

This policy will more specifically address the personal data we collect, transfer, use, and disclose, which generally includes name, address, telephone number, email address, date of birth, billing and payment information, account information, and other information that specifically relates to you, which we collect in the course of providing our marketing communications, goods, and services to you.

### Information We Collect Online

Users under the age of 18 may not be permitted to use certain features of our Websites/Apps, such as click to chat and contact us. 

#### 1\. General Browsing

We collect general information about our visitors’ experience with our Websites/Apps and this general information is not connected to personally identifiable information about individual visitors. This general information (for example, domain type, browser version, service provider or your IP address) will provide us with information regarding the general use of our Websites/Apps. The information collected includes which pages our visitors are viewing on our Websites/Apps and whether visitors arrived through a link for our Websites/Apps. It also includes information on the type of browser and service provider used. For visitors using a mobile version of our Websites, this includes technical information about the device used, such as screen size, cookies supported by the device, and how images may appear. All of this information helps us provide a better experience for our visitors by being able to determine such things as how to best format our mobile Websites/Apps for various devices, our most desired pages, products and features, how to best direct visitors to our Websites/Apps, and where there might be browser or service provider connection issues.

#### 2\. Location Information

Our Website, Apps, and communications may use your IP address to determine the approximate location of your Internet Service Provider (ISP). This allows us to tailor content to you, such as a map of nearby stores. Mobile devices include your cell phone, and could include your laptop or tablet depending on the type of wireless connectivity used. If you do not consent to provide or disable location-based services, we may ask you to manually select the region where you are located, or to enter your zip code; if you chose not to provide this information some features of the Websites, Apps or communications may not be available. See the “Opt-Out” section below for the choices you have regarding collection of location information.

#### 3\. Personal Data

#### Contact Us and Click to Chat

If you complete a general "Contact Us" form on one of our Websites we may collect your name, email address, and any information that you provide in the text of your message.

If you use the Click to Chat feature on our Websites we may collect your name and any additional personal data or other information that you provide throughout the communication.

#### Sign Up for Marketing Email List

If you sign up for our marketing email list, or the marketing email list for any of our affiliate brands, you will be asked to provide your email address. Our affiliate brands are: Abercrombie & Fitch and abercrombie kids. Signing up enables you to receive information about products and offers that we provide via email. Once you sign up you will receive an email to the email address you submitted confirming you are subscribed. In some locations on our Websites/Apps you are given the opportunity to submit additional information, such as gender and date of birth, that will help us cater messaging and marketing emails we send to you. In addition, we may identify you when you click a link in an email to get to our Websites, and may personalize messaging, promotions or product recommendations. You can choose the frequency with which you receive marketing emails or unsubscribe if you no longer want to receive marketing emails from us. See the Opt Out section below for more details.

If you were on the Hollister Co. marketing email list prior to September 2014 and supply your email address on HollisterCo.jp you may receive emails catered to your location.

#### Sending Electronic Postcards or Emailing an Item to a Friend

When you send an electronic postcard, or email an item to a friend from our Websites, the designated recipient will receive your name and email address, as well as any information you entered in the message. The email address information of your recipient is not used for any marketing purposes by us or our affiliate companies unless they have already submitted it for this reason, nor is such information rented, sold or exchanged with third parties for their marketing purposes. We do not review any information provided in the message content. You should not send postcards or items to friends unless you believe your friend would be interested and want to receive the information.

#### My Account

If you are 18 years of age or older you are given the opportunity to create an account on our Websites and Apps. Creating an account requires you to enter your email address, first and last name, and to create a password, and allows you to provide postal addresses, a phone number, payment details, date of birth, gender, and favorite categories. By providing this information we are able to offer you a more personalized experience on our Websites, Apps, and in communications. In addition, we may identify you when you sign into your account and we may personalize messaging, promotions or product recommendations. Some of the features in the account section allow you to create an address book, save a wish list, subscribe to and update your marketing email frequency, access your order history, and enjoy "quick checkouts" by having us automatically enter your name, phone number, email, postal address, and payment details in the checkout process. When you create an account you will receive a welcome email that will be delivered to the email address you inserted into the email field on the create an account page. .

To request to have your account cancelled send an email to Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com from the email address associated with the account you wish to cancel.

#### My Account – Payment Info

If you choose to add a payment type in the account section, you will be able to access this information during checkout when you are signed in. Your preferred payment type will pre-populate during checkout, or you can pick another type by selecting from the drop down list if you choose to save several payment types. If a payment card has expired we will indicate this by highlighting it in red on the Payment Info page, and you can remove this expired payment type and insert a new one if desired. You will have the option to add a new payment type during checkout by ticking a box indicating that you want to store the newly entered payment details in your account. If you reset your account password your payment types will be deleted from your account for security purposes.

#### My Account – Address Book

If you have created an account on our Websites or Apps you may use the personal address book which allows you to save all of the different names and addresses to whom you frequently send purchases or gifts. When you want to send a purchase to someone in your address book, sign into your account and once in checkout you can choose from the saved address list.

#### My Account - Forgot Password

If you forget your password and select to reset it you will be asked to insert the email address for your account so we can send you an email. Once you receive the email click on the link provided and when you are directed to the Website, enter and submit a password that meets the requirements to reset it.

#### My Account - Update Information

When you sign into your account you may be directed to an update information page. In order to proceed to your account you will be required to insert your first and last name, enter a password that meets the requirements, and agree to the legal terms as stated on this page. In addition, if you fill out the needed information on this page and submit it, and you are previously signed up to receive marketing emails, you will now receive marketing emails catered to your location.

#### Sold Out or Product Email Alert

If you provide us with your email address to contact you when a product on the site is available for purchase or to show interest in a product, the email address you submit will only be used for such purpose. The email address will not be used for any additional promotional purposes by us or our affiliate companies, and will be purged after the email(s) are sent or if there is no longer a need to maintain the data. You will, however, be able to sign up to receive marketing emails via a link in the footer of the product alert email that you may receive.

#### Purchasing at the Online Store

If you purchase merchandise through our Websites, we will gather your personal data (including your name, billing and shipping address information, email address, telephone number, banking and payment information), as well as information about your purchases on our Websites, which we may combine with your store purchase information. In addition, if you have created an account you will be able to view your order details in the account section. Some information provided in checkout may be used to personalize a future visit or communications, to cater products or offers to you or shared with affiliates or third parties for our marketing or advertising purposes.

#### Surveys

We will collect information when you fill out a survey offered on our Websites or in communications. This information will assist us in gathering feedback from you in order to improve our services and continue to offer features that you prefer.

#### Social Media Accounts

To create an account on our Websites/Apps or to participate in certain features, our Websites/Apps may allow you to chose to let us access information from accounts you have created on social media sites such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest, Instagram, and other similar sites (“Personal Social Media Accounts”). If you chose to allow us access to your Personal Social Media Accounts, Hollister Co. could collect some, and possibly all, of the data in the Personal Social Media Account to which you grant access. Depending on the terms of the social media site, this information could include: your name, email address, profile picture, gender, networks, user ID, list of friends, date of birth, likes, education history, work history, current city, hometown, interests, relationship status, and location. Once you grant this permission, Hollister Co. will be able to continue to be linked to the permitted Personal Social Media Account and collect information without a further request for permission, which could include later revisions to existing information or new types of information that you add. If you no longer want your Personal Social Media Account(s) linked to our Websites/Apps, click on the ‘disconnect’ link located on our Websites/Apps near the corresponding social media button and we will stop collecting this information. You may also be able to stop our ability to link to information in your Personal Social Media Account by following instructions provided on the applicable social media sites.

This privacy policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of social media sites where you have Personal Social Media Accounts. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the social media sites if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

### Mobile Application

We offer Apps for download to your mobile device that provide you with various interactive features.

The collection and means of collecting information, as well as the use and sharing of information, through any currently existing or future App are discussed in this policy.

In addition:

  * Use of some features of an App will ask for permission to access data on your mobile device, such as your photos. We will only access this data if you provide consent when asked by the App. Please note, some features of the App are only available if you allow us to access the requested content.

  * If you provide consent when asked, the App will send push notifications ("Notifications") to your mobile device. These Notifications can be sent to you and viewed by you even if you are not actively using the App. The Notifications may be specific to your interactions with us and may be location-specific if you have consented to location-based services.

  * See the “Opt-Out” section below for the choices you have regarding collection of location information and data from your mobile device, and receipt of Notifications.

### Information Collected on Pages Hollister Co. Has on Social Media Sites

Personal information may be collected directly by Hollister Co. through social media accounts (“Social Media Pages”) and may also be collected by the social media site hosting the Hollister Co. Social Media Page.

Personal Information collected directly by Hollister Co.: The collection of personal information directly by Hollister Co. on our Social Media Pages will include the type of information addressed under "What is Personal Data" above. Examples of how personal information may be directly collected on Hollister Co. Social Media Pages include providing information through an application or form which has a link to this privacy policy. We will use and share the information we collect on our Social Media Pages in the manner specified below in "Using Information We Collect” and in "Information We Share With Third Parties."

Personal Information collected by the social media sites: This privacy policy does not cover the privacy and security practices of the social media sites on which Hollister Co. has Social Media Pages. Please review privacy policies and terms of service on the social media sites if you have any questions about their privacy or security practices.

The social media sites where Hollister Co. has Social Media Pages may provide aggregate information and analysis to Hollister Co. about your use of our Social Media Pages. This allows us to better understand and analyze our user growth, general demographic information about the users of our Social Media Pages, and interaction with content on our Social Media Pages. Overall, this information may be used to help us understand the types of visitors and users of our Social Media Pages and use of the content.

### Using Information We Collect

We use the information collected through our Websites, Apps, and communications for the following purposes:

  * To fulfill orders and complete transactions, including for processing payments and refunds, verifying addresses, and to ship merchandise.

  * To conduct appropriate anti-fraud checks in the course of which the personal information that you provide may be disclosed to a credit reference or fraud prevention agency, which may keep a record of that information.

  * To detect and protect us, our affiliate companies and other third parties against negligence, fraud, theft, and other illegal activities and to audit compliance with our and their internal policies.

  * To comply with administrative, tax, investigative or other audit requirements or any other legal or regulatory disclosure requirements.

  * As required by applicable laws, rules, and regulations, and to comply with any legal or regulatory requirements.

  * To monitor and analyze your activity with us, interaction with our Websites, Apps, communications, and the effectiveness of our advertising and your purchases.

  * To serve site content, including search engine options, personalized messaging, product recommendations, and interactive features on our Websites, Apps, and in communications.

  * To assist you with any questions or requests you may have regarding our Websites and Apps - or through any form of contact you make with us, including by email, phone, postal mail or via our Websites.

  * To develop, market, sell, and provide our products, services, communications, advertising, and other areas associated with our Websites, Apps, and stores.

  * To provide communications to you, such as operational communications (associated with your order, account, and other interactions with our Websites and Apps) and marketing communications (for example regarding: coming soon, sold out, cart abandonment, product view, appeasement, product recommendations, banners, promotions, services, offers, and events).

  * To understand your needs and preferences in order to personalize your experience of our Websites, Apps, store visits, marketing communications, and advertising regarding our products and services as well as our affiliated companies’ products and services.

  * To conduct surveys, sweepstakes or contests.

  * To provide location based information, marketing, and advertisements on our Websites and Apps, in communications, in search engines, on third party websites, and when you visit our stores.

  * To create, administer, and update your account(s) that you have set up on our Websites and Apps, including using features offered in the account section.

  * To manage and develop our business and operations, and those of our affiliated companies.

  * To consider you for employment, and administer and maintain application information provided.

Please note that if you do not provide us with the required personal information, we may not be able to provide the information, products or services you need or process your request.

### Information We Share With Third Parties

#### 1\. Email Addresses

We do not sell, or grant rights to external third parties, to use your email address for their own marketing purposes.

Please note, if you request to be removed from our email marketing list, you may still receive email confirmations from us regarding any orders placed by you on our Websites, or other operational emails.

#### 2\. Postal Addresses

We make the names and postal addresses in our postal mailing list, sometimes categorized by purchasing information, available to our affiliates (for example, Abercrombie & Fitch and abercrombie kids) and other unaffiliated companies for their marketing purposes. See the “Opt-Out” section below for instructions on how to opt out of sharing with unaffiliated companies.

#### 3\. Service Providers

Please be aware that we may share information collected with third parties to assist us with our e-commerce business, such as our Websites, Apps, and communications, and our Social Media Pages. Some examples of the assistance that may be provided by third party service providers are: fulfilling orders (including but not limited to, processing payments, assisting with shipment, providing fraud prevention services, and verifying addresses), providing advertising services - including on social media sites and internet search engines, sending marketing communications, your actions in response to our communications and the effectiveness of our advertising, monitoring and analyzing site activity, serving site content (including a site search feature, product options, and personalized messaging), organizing information, conducting surveys, administering and maintaining employment application information, offering interactive features on our App, evaluating potential models, and administering emails, sweepstakes or contests. Such third parties may have access to your personal data to provide services on our behalf, but may not use your information for any other purpose.

#### 4\. Legal Disclosures

You should also be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if we are required, or we genuinely believe that we are required, to do so by law or if we reasonably consider that it is necessary to protect the users of our Websites and Apps and that it is difficult to obtain consent from you. In the event that we, or our parent company, are acquired by a new owner, or if following a reorganization of our corporate group we become part of one of our affiliate companies, your information may be transferred to a new owner, or another of our affiliate companies, as part of our assets. If this occurs, we will take all reasonable steps to ensure that our new owner or the affiliate which we become part of will use your personal data only in accordance with the terms of this privacy policy.

#### 5\. Sharing Information within our Group

We may disclose the information that you provide to us (including, without limitation, your personal data) to any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and the subsidiaries of our holding company (including our affiliated companies). HCo and its affiliates will not subscribe you to their ongoing marketing email or text message programs unless you have separately consented to receive such marketing emails or texts from a given affiliate. These members may use information provided by you for marketing purposes or to serve personalized messaging on our Websites, Apps, and communications.

### Storage of Information

All of the information gathered through our Websites, Apps, and communications that you provide to us is sent to the United States and Japan. We store and process your personal data and any other information that we collect from you through our Websites, Apps, and communications in the United States, Japan, and Japan. Our third party service providers who offer services to us from time to time may also store and process your personal data in the United States, Japan, and Japan. We, and our third party service providers mentioned above, may need to disclose your personal data that we store if required to do so under any applicable laws, rules or regulations.

### Cookies and Advertising

#### 1\. What Are Cookies, Pixel Tags and URL Links, and How Are These Used on Our Websites or in Our Emails?

Our Websites use, and our third party service providers may use, a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer or device. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive or mobile device. The information collected when visiting our Websites may include the following: an IP address, the URL of the page from which you arrived; your browser type; other technical information about your device used to visit our Websites; the pages you view; the features you use; whether you create an account, or sign in and where you go on our Websites once signed in; whether you complete a transaction; whether you have previously completed a survey; and the time of your visit. This information allows us to determine such things as which parts of our Websites are most visited or used, what products are browsed and/or purchased, the effectiveness of the Websites, your specific interaction with our Websites, and difficulties you may experience in accessing our Websites. With this knowledge, we can improve the quality of your experience on our Websites by recognizing and delivering more of the most desired features and information, personalize your experience, and resolve access difficulties. In addition, our Websites use cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, whether you purchase any or all of those items, and to tell us whether you have visited one of our Websites in the past. This allows you to maintain shopping carts between visits and allows us to inquire about your continued interest in items in your shopping cart or that you viewed on one of our Websites. Our Websites also use cookies to help keep track of checkout information, other than payment method information, while you remain on our Websites. In addition, the information collected by us or our service provider(s) may be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you from your visits to our Websites.

Our Websites use, and our third party service providers may also use, Pixel Tags (also known as Web beacons, Web bugs, and Clear GIFs) on the Websites and in emails. A Pixel Tag is a nearly invisible pixel-sized graphic image on a Webpage or email message. Pixel Tags may be used to collect the same information about your visit that is collected through cookies, as noted above. We may also collect information about a search engine used, and a search engine advertisement clicked to navigate to the Websites. Pixel Tags in emails help us confirm the receipt of, and response to, our emails (including your interaction with our Websites as a result of receiving the email) and the time our email is viewed. This information helps us to make similar evaluations about our Websites and emails as with cookies and to determine the most desired features and information so that we can provide those features and information to you and personalize our interactions with you. This information may also be linked to and combined with information that we collect about you from your visits to our Websites.

In addition, our email communications to you may include a "click-through URL" linked to a particular page on one of our Websites. By clicking on one of the URLs, you will automatically enter one of our Websites and we may collect information related to the "click-through". You may avoid having this information collected by not clicking on the URL links in our email communications.

#### 2.How Third Parties Serve You Our Advertisements On Other Websites and Your Choices

We contract with third party advertising companies to serve you online display and banner advertisements on other websites. To serve this advertising, these third parties may place, use or rely on technology, such as cookies and/or Pixel Tags, to collect information about your interactions with our Websites and Apps and interactions with other websites. These advertising companies may use and share the information gathered to deliver our ads more tailored to your interests on other websites that are a part of their online advertising networks and/or search engines. We receive aggregate information from these third parties to gauge our advertising effectiveness. To opt out you can click on the icon that may appear on some of our advertising served through these technologies. We may use more than one third party company for placing this advertising, which would require you to opt out of each company.

### Consent

By submitting your personal data to us through our Websites, Apps, and communications, you are agreeing that we may collect, use and disclose your personal data in accordance with the purposes and uses identified in this policy.

### Opt-Out

#### 1\. Collection of Location Information

a. _Mobile Device Location Information Through our Mobile Sites and Apps._ Your mobile device may allow you to disable location-based services on your device, which will prevent our Websites and Apps from accessing your mobile device location information. For specific questions regarding disabling your device's location services, we recommend you review the specific instructions provided for your mobile device. Note that some features on our Websites and Apps may not be available if you disable location-based services.

b. _Desktop Device Location Information Through Website Features._ Your desktop web browser may allow you to remove permission you granted through your desktop device for our Websites to access your location information and/or completely block requests for location information. For specific questions regarding disabling your browser’s location services, we recommend you review the specific instructions provided with your browser

c. _Location Information Through Email._ Your email program may allow you to prevent the images in the emails you receive from us from downloading, which will also prevent our service provider from accessing your location information. You can also unsubscribe from receiving our emails, as described in the Email Address section below.

#### 2\. Email Address

If you no longer wish to receive emails from us, please [click here](https://www.hollisterco.jp/en_JP/unsubscribe) to enter your email address and unsubscribe from receiving our marketing emails. To unsubscribe from receiving marketing emails from any of our relevant affiliate companies' brands, go to the email and phone page within the “My Account” section, click on the drop-down menu and select ‘No emails/Unsubscribe’ for the brand from which you no longer want to receive marketing emails, and press ‘SUBMIT.' Or, click on the unsubscribe link located in the footer of the marketing email to be directed to the unsubscribe page to submit your email address.

Please note, if you request to be removed from our email marketing list, you may still receive email confirmations from us regarding any orders placed on our Websites or other operational emails.

If you have any problems with unsubscribing from marketing emails please contact us:

Responsible Sender of Marketing Emails  
Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc.  
6301 Fitch Path  
New Albany, Ohio 43054 USA  
Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com

#### 3.Postal Address

If you do not wish to receive marketing materials from us via postal mail, please email us at Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com and tell us to remove you from our postal mailing list, including the postal address you wish to have removed.

If you would like to make sure that we do not disclose your name and postal mailing address to unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes, please email us at [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com ](mailto:Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com)and ask us not to share your postal address with unaffiliated companies, including the postal address

### Accessing and Updating Your Personal Data

We prefer to keep personal data of those who create an account on our Websites and Apps accurate and up to date. To do this, we provide you with the opportunity to update or modify your personal data. Just sign into your account with your email address and password, and you will see an overview page where you can update your information. You may also email or write to us if you think that personal data that we hold about you needs to be updated.

Upon your written request, we will inform you of the personal data relating to you that we hold and the use and general disclosure of your personal data. We will also give you a copy of the personal data we have retained.

Please send your written request to the email address or postal address provided under "Questions About Privacy" below. In your written request, please include your name, address, phone number, and email address so that we may verify whether we retain any personal data about you.

### Privacy of Children

Our Websites are not directed at children under the age of 18, and we do not knowingly collect any personal information from children under the age of 18. No one under the age of 18 should provide personal data on our Websites or at our stores. In the past Hollister Co. collected personal information from children under the age of 18 with the consent of the child’s parent or guardian. Any such personal information collected by Hollister Co. has been deleted, and Hollister Co. no longer has any information concerning that child. 

### Links

For your convenience and enjoyment, our Websites and Apps may contain links to other websites operated by third parties ("Third Party Sites"). We do not monitor and are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Third Party Sites. We would urge you to review the privacy policies of each Third Party Site to ensure that you are comfortable with the privacy policies and practices.

### Updates to Privacy Policy

As we continue to offer our customers new and different types of content and services, we may revise this privacy policy to reflect the changes that we have made to our information collection, use, disclosure or transfer practices. We will notify you that we have revised our privacy policy by placing a notice on our Websites/Apps. Should there be a material change to our information collection, use or disclosure practices, it will be applied only to information collected on a going forward basis. By submitting personal data to us after the changes coming into effect, you are agreeing that we may collect, use, disclose, and transfer your personal data in accordance with the purposes and uses identified and to the transferees specified in the updated privacy policy.

### Security Statement

We limit the number of employees that have access to the databases that contain personal information.

Our Websites are designed to accept orders from web browsers that allow communication through Transport Layer Security (TLS) v1.1 and 1.2. We support Microsoft Internet Explorer 11.0+, Apple OS X 10.9+, Android 5.0+, and Apple iOS 9.0+. We recommend if you are viewing our websites on Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox to download the latest version in order to maximize your experience, otherwise you may not be able to access or utilize all pages on our websites as intended.

While we implement the above security measures on our Websites/Apps, you should be aware that 100% security is not always possible.

### Questions About Privacy

If, for any reason, you are accessing a country specific website for a country in which you are not located (e.g. utilizing a proxy server) please contact Customer Service to view the policies and terms specific to your jurisdiction.

If you have any questions, comments or concerns regarding our privacy practices or our legal compliance with the Japanese Act on Protection of Personal Information or other applicable privacy law or regulation, please email us at [Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com](mailto:Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com) or write to us at the address set out below:

Attn: Privacy Policy Manager  
Abercrombie & Fitch Stores, Inc.  
6301 Fitch Path  
New Albany, Ohio 43054 USA

Privacy_Policy@HollisterCo.com
